<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <eleven>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your Inner Behaviour number is:</span>11</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An Behaviour number of 11 means:</span>You Behaviour is of casting the light of illumination; of being the true idealist. You secretly believe there is more to life than we can know or prove, and you would like to be provider of the 'word' from on high.</p></div>]]>
  </eleven>
  <twentytwo>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your Inner Behaviour number is:</span>22</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 22 means:</span>You Behaviour is of being a master organizer and a builder of monumental projects; of guiding a truly huge endeavor. Your secret fantasy is to think big and imagine what could be done for the world. You may also Behaviour of the huge rewards.</p></div>]]>
  </twentytwo>
  <one>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your Inner Behaviour number is:</span>1</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An Behaviour number of 1 means:</span>You Behaviour is of being a leader and one who is in charge. You want to be known for your courage, daring, and original ideas. You seek unconquered heights. People may get a first impression that you are very aggressive and sure of yourself.</p></div>]]>
  </one>
  <two>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>2</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 2 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of close and meaningful relationships, cooperation with those around you; family and friends. You want to be a peacemaker and mediator. You present an image that you are a very pliable and easygoing person who would be very easy to get along with.</p></div>]]>
  </two>
  <three>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>3</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 3 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of artistic expression; writing, painting, music. You would seek to more freely express your  feeling and obtain more enjoyment from life. You also Behaviour of being more popular, likable, and appreciated.</p></div>]]>
  </three>
  <four>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>4</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 4 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of being a very solid citizen that people can depend upon. You strive for organization and predictable order. You want to be recognized as a person with a plan and the discipline to make that plan work like clockwork.</p></div>]]>
  </four>
  <five>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>5</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 5 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of being totally free and unrestrained by responsibility. You see yourself conversing and mingling with the natives in many nations, living for adventure and life experiences. You imagine what you might accomplished.</p></div>]]>
  </five>
  <six>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>6</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 6 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of guiding and fostering the perfect family in the perfect home. You crave the devotion from offspring and a loving spouse. You picture yourself in the center of a successful domestic unit.</p></div>]]>
  </six>
  <seven>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>7</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 7 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of having the opportunity to read, study, and shut yourself off from worldly distractions. You can see yourself as a teacher, mystic, or ecclesiastic, spending your life in the pursuit of knowledge and learning.</p></div>]]>
  </seven>
  <eight>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>8</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 8 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of success in the business or political world, of power and control of large material endeavors. You crave authority and recognition of executive skills. Your secret self may have very strong desire to become an entrepreneur.</p></div>]]>
  </eight>
  <nine>
    <![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400"><p><span fontWeight="bold"  fontSize="20">Your  Behaviour number is:</span>9</p><p><span fontWeight="bold">An  Behaviour number of 9 means:</span>Your Behaviour is of being creative, intellectual, and universal; the selfless humanitarian. You understand the needy and want to help them. You would love to be a person people count on for support and advice.</p></div>]]>
  </nine>
</data>
