<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<main>
<tag><![CDATA[<div paragraphSpaceAfter="10" color = "0x3b1400">
<p><span fontWeight="bold" fontSize="14">Numerology</span>is any of many systems, traditions or beliefs in a mystical or esoteric relationship between numbers and physical objects or living things.</p>
<p>Numerology and numerological divination by systems such as isopsephy were popular among early mathematicians, such as Pythagoras, but are no longer considered part of mathematics and are regarded as pseudomathematics by modern scientists. This is similar to the historical relationships between astrology and astronomy, and between alchemy and chemistry.</p>
<p>Today, numerology is often associated with the occult, alongside astrology and similar divinatory arts</p>
<p>The term can also be used for those who place excess faith in numerical patterns, even if those people don't practice traditional numerology. For example, in his 1997 book Numerology: Or What Pythagoras Wrought, mathematician Underwood Dudley uses the term to discuss practitioners of the</p>
<p><span fontWeight="bold">Alphabetic systems</span></p>
<p>There are many numerology systems which assign numerical value to the letters of an alphabet. Examples include the Abjad numerals in Arabic, the Hebrew numerals, Armenian numerals, and Greek numerals. The practice within Jewish tradition of assigning mystical meaning to words based on their numerical values, and on connections between words of equal value, is known as gematria.</p>
<p><span fontWeight="bold">1= a, j, s; 2= b, k, t; 3= c, l, u; 4= d, m, v; 5= e, n, w; 6= f, o, x; 7= g, p, y; 8= h, q, z; 9= i, r</span></p>
<p>...and are then summed.</p>
<p><span fontWeight="bold">Examples:</span></p>
<p>* 3,489 → 3 + 4 + 8 + 9 = 24 → 2 + 4 = 6</p>
<p>* Hello → 8 + 5 + 3 + 3 + 6 = 25 → 2 + 5 = 7</p>
<p>A quicker way to arrive at a single-digit summation (the digital root) is simply to take the value modulo 9, substituting a 0 result with 9 itself.</p>
<p>Different methods of calculation exist, including Chaldean, Pythagorean, Hebraic, Helyn Hitchcock's method, Phonetic, Japanese, Arabic and Indian.</p>
<p>The examples above are calculated using decimal (base 10) arithmetic. Other number systems exist, such as binary, octal, hexadecimal and vigesimal; summing digits in these bases yields different results. The first example, shown above, appears thus when rendered in octal (base 8)</p>
<p><span fontWeight="bold">* 3,48910 = 66418 → 6 + 6 + 4 + 1 = 218 → 2 + 1 = 38 = 310</span></p>
<p><span fontWeight="bold">Pythagorean system</span></p>
<p>Pythagoras was never involved in the numerology systems known nowadays. He was actually a philosopher who contributed with the concept of numbers as symbols rather than mere numerals, but numerology as we know it is a system based on Gematria, which is one of the Cabbalistic disciplines. Through Gematria one can get the number of each word or name, since the Hebrew alphabet has the same symbols for both letters and numbers. Western numerology is but a way to adapt the principles of Gematria into the Latin alphabet so as to get the numbers of words and names as well.</p>
</div>
]]>
</tag></main>